http://www.getrevue.co/privacy/platform?ref=Revue+Profile

Log in
Revue Holding B.V. ("Revue"; "we"), situated in The Netherlands provides services to the users of our platform and subscribers ("you"). Our services include activities relating to providing a tool that allows writers and publishers to create and send out newsletters, as well as other services ("the Services"). We process personal data during the undertaking of these Services.
Revue deems careful handling of personal data to be paramount. Personal data is carefully processed and secured. When processing, we adhere to the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (the “Rules"). This Privacy Statement relates to personal information collected by, or under the control of Revue, in accordance with the Rules. Our data processing terms are available here.
In this Privacy Statement, we summarise what personal data we collect and use and for what purpose. We advise you to read our Privacy Statement carefully. This Privacy Statement applies to our Revue platform, related sites, apps, communications and services.
This Privacy Statement was last altered on the 24th May 2018.
Use of Personal Data
By using our Services, you may share your personal data with us. We exclusively collect and use the personal data that is provided to us by you, or your organisation. Revue will not use your personal data for other purposes than for which you, or your organisation, have given us permission beforehand.
Types of Data Collected
When using our Services, we may collect the following Information about you:
Personal identification data: name, surname;
Contact information data: email, address;
Images/videos from which you may be identified;
Other provided data: IP address, payment information, social media accounts, feedback and other communication.
Purposes of Processing
Personal data is generally processed by Revue for the following purposes:
Logging in and verifying/authenticating users of the Service;
Sending and delivering messages, newsletters, and other communication via the Service;
Communication between Revue, platform users, and their audience;
Monitoring and auditing the Service;
Analysing statistics and optimising the Service.
We collect your personal data based on legitimate business interests, performance of a contract between you and Revue, or consent. If the processing is based on consent, it can be withdrawn at any time.
Subscription to Services
Newsletters created with the use of our Services can be subscribed to directly or indirectly. Individuals can directly subscribe via signup forms or plugins. Indirect subscription is possible through third-party (such as Mailchimp, Zapier) lists or manual import. Indirect subscription is only allowed with the individuals’ consent. Revue instructs the platform users to collect valid consent for subscription and puts measures in place to prevent unauthorised direct marketing. However, ensuring the validity of subscribers’ consent is the responsibility of each platform user. Newsletters sent via our platform always contain a possibility to opt-out.
Data Storage
In principle, we only keep your data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes described in this Privacy Statement. As a general rule, we store personal data of our platform users until the platform user terminates its account.
Your Rights
You have the right to request access to the information we have about you. You can do this by contacting us directly. We will make sure to provide you with a copy of your data that we process in a machine-readable format. We may need to verify your identity to comply with your request.
If you believe that the information we have about you is incorrect, you can contact us, so we can update the information to ensure it is accurate. You also have the right to object to certain data processing operations, such as direct marketing. If at any point you wish for us to delete information about you, you can communicate it to us.
You can contact us at any time with these requests and we will respond in a timely manner applicable with the Rules. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received from us, you may then refer your complaint to the relevant supervisory authority.
Provision to Third Parties
We will not provide the data you have provided us to other parties if you have not given us permission to do so, unless this is necessary within the framework of the execution of the contractual agreement you, or your organisation, have taken out with us or if this is required by the law.
Data Transfers
For the fulfilment of the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Statement, your data may be transferred outside the European Economic Area. Whenever this is the case, we make sure that personal data is transferred in a secure manner. For transfers to the US, we ensure that the party is subject to the US-EU Privacy Shield Agreement. For other transfers, your data may be transferred to countries recognized by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of data protection.
Cookies and Analytics
For the functioning of our platform, it is necessary that Revue makes use of functional cookies. Additionally, when you use our service, your IP address is automatically saved in the log files of our web server. This is necessary to allow us to properly manage and secure our Services. We do not use your IP address to follow and register your behaviour online. Normally, we are not able to link your IP address to your name, address or other identifying information, except when you actively provide us with such information and continue to make use of the same IP address.
In addition to cookies, we perform email analytics and track if you find the e-mails of our users interesting. This way we can provide our users with relevant information.
User data that you provide may be kept for making statistical analyses including via Google Analytics. These statistics are used to optimise our Services. Wherever possible, we make this data pseudonymized.
Security
We take security measures in order to limit misuse of and unauthorised access to personal data. We take the measures including, but not limited to:
Logical access control, use of passwords and possibly a second factor;
Encryption of data;
Pseudonymising data;
Securing data during the exchange of it, making use of the HTTPS protocol, except if the platform user opts to use a different domain;
Purpose-bound access limitations;
Control of acknowledged authorisations.
Special information for parents
We do not provide our Services directly to, nor collect personal data of, children below the age of 16.
If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with their personal information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from children under age of 16 without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Third Party Websites
This statement does not apply to third party websites that are visited from our Services through links. We cannot guarantee that these third parties will handle your personal data safely and reliably. We advise you to read the privacy statements of these third parties before making use of them.
Revue Holding B.V.
Europalaan 500-unit O.2.3,
3526KS Utrecht,
The Netherlands
